A Guide to the Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files, 1976-1977
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the President of the University of Virginia, Office Administrative Files 1976-1977
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
RG-2/1/2.791
This collection consists of 13,000 items.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Access restrictions may apply to specific student records under the terms of the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (F.E.R.P.A.).
Acquisition Information
This collection was transferred to the library on 1979 September 10.
Scope and Content Information
These files constitute the major record series generated by the president of the University of Virginia. The records consist chiefly of correspondence, but also include reports, minutes, clippings, memoranda, and related papers concerning all areas of business of the president's office.
The papers consist of: general and administrative committee files.
Organization
SERIES I: General Records, 1976-1977, Boxes 1-27
SERIES II: Administrative Committees, 1976-1977, Boxes 28-29
Contents List
- Series I: General Records
  - "A-Al" Miscellaneous--Acosta, H. re: Honor System; Henry Adams Papers; Adult Education Association; Albemarle County Fire Marshal re: Disposal of Wastes from Vivarium 1976-1977 (Box Box 1)
  - "Am" Miscellaneous--Correspondence with Various National Associations, such as American Cancer Society; American Civil Liberties Union re: Media Board 1976-1977 (Box Box 1)
  - "An-Az" Miscellaneous--Correspondence with A. Armstrong re: Queen's Visit 1976-1977 (Box Box 1)
  - Admissions--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 1)
  - Admissions--College "A-Bo" (2 folders) (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 1)
  - Admissions--College "Br-Hi" (6 folders) (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 2)
  - Admissions--College "Ho-Ph" (6 folders) (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 3)
  - Admissions--College "Po-We" (6 folders) (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 4)
  - Admissions--College "Wh-Z" (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 5)
  - Admissions--Graduate (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 5)
  - Admissions--Law "A-J" (6 folders) (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 5)
  - Admissions--Law "K-Z" (4 folders) (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 6)
  - Admissions--Law--Cases of No Interest (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 6)
  - Admissions--Medical (2 folders) (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 6)
  - Admissions--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 7)
  - Admissions--Sensitive Lists, Legacies (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 7)
  - Afro-American Studies--Library Controversy 1976-1977 (Box Box 7)
  - Alumni Association--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 7)
  - Alumni Fund 1976-1977 (Box Box 7)
  - American Association of State Colleges and Universities 1976-1977 (Box Box 7)
  - American Association of University Professors 1976-1977 (Box Box 7)
  - American Council on Education 1976-1977 (Box Box 7)
  - Annual Reports 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Annual Reports--President's 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Anthropology 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Applications "A-F" (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Applications "G-P" (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Applications "R-Z" (Restricted) 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Architecture--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Architecture--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Army--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Army--Judge Advocate General's School 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Art--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 8)
  - Art--Bayly Museum 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Art--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Asian Studies Consortium 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Association of American Colleges 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Association of American Universities (2 folders) 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Association of Virginia Colleges 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Astronomy 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Athletics--General (2 folders) 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Athletics--ACC 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Athletics--College Football Association 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Athletics--Finances 1976-1977 (Box Box 9)
  - Athletics--National Collegiate Athletic Association 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - Athletics--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - Attorney General--State--Freedom of Information Act vs Privacy Protection 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - Automated Data Processing 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - Auxiliary and Business Services 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - "Ba-Bm" Miscellaneous--Black Student Alliance 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - "Bn-Bz" Miscellaneous--Brooks Hall History 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - Biology--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - Biology--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - Buildings and Grounds 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - Business and Finance 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - Business Manager 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - "Ca-Cha" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - "Che-Col" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 10)
  - "Com-Cou" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - "Cr-Cz" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Cavalier Daily--Ken Easley Problem, Reconsideration of Media Board 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Chemistry 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Civil Rights 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Classics 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Clinch Valley College--Possible Break between Clinch Valley and the University 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - College Entrance Examination Board 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - College of Arts and Sciences 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Commerce--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Commerce--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Community Colleges 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Comptroller--State 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Computer Activities 1976-1977 (Box Box 11)
  - Consortium--Central Virginia 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Consortium--Northern Virginia 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Consortium--Tidewater 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Consortium--Valley 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Consortium--Western 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Continuing Education--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Continuing Education--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Continuing Education--Northern Virginia Center 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Council of Presidents 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Council of Southern Universities 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - "Da-Dz" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Danforth Foundation 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Darden Graduate School of Business--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 12)
  - Darden Graduate School of Business--Sponsors 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Darden Graduate School of Business--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Dean's Meetings 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Defense, U.S. Department of 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Degrees 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Development 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Development--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Dramas 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - DuPont Regional 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - "Ea-En" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - "Eq-Ez" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Economics 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Education--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Education--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Energy Office--State 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Energy Research and Development Administration 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Engineering and Applied Science--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Engineering--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Engineering Research Laboratories for Engineering Sciences 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - Engineering and Buildings--State 1976-1977 (Box Box 13)
  - English 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - Enrollment 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - Environmental Sciences 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - Equal Opportunity Programs 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - Equal Opportunity--Affirmative Action (2 folders) 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - "Fa-Fi" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - "Fl-Fz" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - Faculty--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - Faculty of Arts and Sciences 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - Federal Executive Institute 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - Fellowships and Scholarships--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 14)
  - Fellowships--Love 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - Fellowships--Rhodes 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - Financial Aid to Students 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - French Literature and Linguistics 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - House Appropriations 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - "G" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - General Assembly 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - German Language and Literature 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - Gifts and Grants, A-Z (2 folders) 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - Government and Foreign Affairs 1976-1977 (Box Box 15)
  - Governor's Office 1976-1977 (Box Box 16)
  - Governor--Administration 1976-1977 (Box Box 16)
  - Governor--Education (2 folders) 1976-1977 (Box Box 16)
  - Governor--Human Resources 1976-1977 (Box Box 16)
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences 1976-1977 (Box Box 16)
  - Guggenheim Foundation 1976-1977 (Box Box 16)
  - "Ha-He" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 16)
  - "Hi-Hz" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 16)
  - Health, Education and Welfare, U.S. Department of 1976-1977 (Box Box 16)
  - Hereford, Frank L., Jr. 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Hereford-- Farmington 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Hereford--Taiwan Trip 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Higher Education Act of 1965 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Higher Education Act--Title I 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Higher Education Act--Title III 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Higher Education Act--Title IV 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Higher Education Act--Title IX 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Highway Department 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - History 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Honor System and Committee 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - Housing 1976-1977 (Box Box 17)
  - "I" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Institute of Government--Bert Lance Invitation 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Institutional Analysis 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Intergovernmental Affairs 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Interlock, Inc. 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - "J" Miscellaneous--Jefferson Papers 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Thomas Jefferson Memorial Foundation 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Judiciary Committee 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - "K" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - "L" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Law--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Law--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Law School Foundation 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Law School Center for Oceans Law and Policy 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Lawn Society 1976-1977 (Box Box 18)
  - Legal Advisor 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - Library--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - Library--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - Library Associates 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - "Mc" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - "Mac-Mar" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - "Mas-Mey" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - "Mi-Mu" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - McGregor Fund 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - Madison House 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - Management Analysis and Systems Development--Information Systems 1976-1977 (Box Box 19)
  - Mariners Museum (3 folders) 1976-1977 (Box Box 20)
  - Mary Washington College 1976-1977 (Box Box 20)
  - Mathematics 1976-1977 (Box Box 20)
  - Medical Center--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 20)
  - Medical Center--Hospital 1976-1977 (Box Box 20)
  - Medical Center--Hospital Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 20)
  - Medical Center--Nursing 1976-1977 (Box Box 20)
  - Medical Center--Nursing Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 20)
  - Medical Center--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 20)
  - Medical School--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 20)
  - Medical School--Advisory Committee Faculty Meetings 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - Medical School--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - Music 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - "Na" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - "Ne-Nz" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - National Aeronautics and Space Administration 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC) 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - National Association of State Universities and Land-Grant Colleges (NASULGC)--For Your Information 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - National Medal of Science 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - National Science Foundation 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - Naval Academy of the United States 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - Newcomb Hall 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - "O" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - Omicron Delta Kappa 1976-1977 (Box Box 21)
  - "P" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Parking and Transit 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Personnel--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Personnel--Employee Relations 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Personnel and Training (State), Department of 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Phi Beta Kappa 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Philosophy 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Physical Planning 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Physics--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Physics--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Planning and Budget--State (3 folders) 1976-1977 (Box Box 22)
  - Planning and Budget--Capital Outlay 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget--Medical 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Planning and Budget--University of Virginia 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Planning Project Status Reports 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Printing Office 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Promotions 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Provost of University 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Psychology 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Purchasing 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - "Q" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Queen's Visit, July 10, 1976 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - "R" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Recommendations, A-Z 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Registrar 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - Religious Studies 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - ROTC--General 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - ROTC--Air Force 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - ROTC--Army 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - ROTC--Navy 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - "Sa-Se" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - "Sh-Sl" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 23)
  - "Sm-Sp" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - "St-Sz" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Senate--University 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Seven Society 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Slavic Languages and Literature 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Sociology 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Southern Association of Colleges and Schools 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Southern Association of Land-Grant Colleges and State Universities 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Southern Regional Education Board 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Space Administrator 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Space Administrator--Analysis and Reports 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Spanish, Italian, Portuguese 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Speech Communications 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Speeches--Current 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - Sponsored Programs 1976-1977 (Box Box 24)
  - State Council of Higher Education (SCHE) (6 folders) 1976-1977 (Box Box 25)
  - State Department of Education 1976-1977 (Box Box 25)
  - Student Affairs (2 folders) 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - Student Affairs--Personnel 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - Student Council 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - State Health Department 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - Summer Sessions 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - "Ta-Ti" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - "To-Tu" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - Tayloe Murphy Institute 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - Travel Invoices--President 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - Treasurer--University 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - "U" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - Universities Research Association 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - University Center in Virginia 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - University Police 1976-1977 (Box Box 26)
  - University Press of Virginia 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - University Relations 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - University Relations--Medical Center Information 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - University Union 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - Upward Bound 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - Urban Observatory Program 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - "V" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - Virginia Academy of Science 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - Virginia Student Aid Foundation 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - "Wa-Web" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - "Wed-Wil" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - "Win-Wx" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
  - "X-Y-Z" Miscellaneous 1976-1977 (Box Box 27)
- Series II: Administrative Committees
  - Ad Hoc--Search for Dean of Afro-American Affairs 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Ad Hoc--Selection of Vice-President for Health Sciences Medical Center 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Ad Hoc--Search for Director Institutional Analysis 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Ad Hoc--Search for Dean of Law School 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Ad Hoc--Search for Dean of School of Medicine 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Ad Hoc--Resident Advisor's Qualifications--Work of Committee 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Ad Hoc--Resident Advisor's Qualifications--Replies to Letters 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Admissions 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Afro-American Affairs Advisory 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Algernon Sydney Sullivan Awards 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Arboretum 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Architectural Advisory 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Advisory--Archives and Records 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Athletic Advisory Council 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Calendar 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Career Planning and Placement 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Catalogue 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Cemetery 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Chapel 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Commencement and Convocations 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Commencement and Convocations--Subcommittee--Processions 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Commencement and Convocations--Subcommittee--Public Occasions 1976-1977 (Box Box 28)
  - Community Colleges 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Computers 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Danforth Fellowships 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Development 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Education and Employment Opportunities, Obligations, and Rights 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Energy Conservation 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Fraternities and Sororities 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Fulbright Grants 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Graduate Opportunities 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Graphics 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Gwathmey Award 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Housing 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - International Students 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Thomas Jefferson Award 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Lectures--Page, Barbour, and Richard 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Lectures--Special 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Library 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Master Plan 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Minority Student Affairs Advisory Council 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Names 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Patents 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Radiation Safety 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Registration 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Rhodes Scholarships 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - ROTC 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Scheduling 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Security and General Safety 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Security and General Safety--Subcommittee--Laser Safety Disposal Hazardous Materials 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Scholarships, Grants-in-Aid, Loans and Employment 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Student Activities 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Student Health 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Student Rights and Responsibilities 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Summer Grants 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Summer Session 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Teacher Education 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Traffic Appeals 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Traffic and Parking 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - University Committee on Students 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - University Press 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - University Union 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Virginia Quarterly Review 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)
  - Virginia Status of University Students 1976-1977 (Box Box 29)